American Dialect Society Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Narrative Transcriptions
    - Craw, R.E. [Rebecca Ellen Craw]. (Folder 85)
      (Westport, MA; AFS 24724)
    - Crawford, H.B. [Hattie B. Crawford]. (Folder 86)
      (Lancaster, NH; AFS 25446, 25448, 25450)
    - Crosby, G. (Folder 87)
      (Bellerica, MA; AFS 24559)
    - Curren, Mary Y. (Folder 88)
      (Calais, ME; AFS 25256)
    - Dwinell, J.W. (Box 19, Folder 89)
      (Topsfield, MA; AFS 24566, 24468)
    - Fiske, A.W. [Arthur W. Fiske]. (Folder 90)
      (Granby, MA; AFS 24892)
    - Fitzherbert, Mrs. M. [Martha Lunday Fitzherbert]. (Folder 91)
      (Fort Fairfield, ME; AFS 25284, 25286)
    - Gardner, E. (Folder 92)
      (Hingham, MA; AFS 24532, 24534)
    - George, L.E.E. [Lizzie Evelyn E. George]. (Folder 93)
      (Kingston, NH; AFS 25110, 25112)
    - Gerow, C.F. [Charles F. Gerow]. (Folder 94)
      (Bethel, CT; AFS 24914, 25050, 25051)
    - Gifford, J. [John Gifford]. (Folder 95)
      (South Westport, CT; AFS 24727)
    - Giles, R. [Richard Giles]. (Folder 96)
      (Cummington, MA; AFS 24953)
    - Gold, C.L. [Charles L. Gold]. (Folder 97)
      (West Cornwall, CT; AFS 25007, 25009, 25011, 25013)
    - Goodell, F.H. [Fred H. Goodell]. (Folder 98)
      (South Williamstown, MA; AFS 24961, 24963, 24965, 24967
    - Goslee, H.C. [Henry C. Goslee]. (Folder 99)
      (Morris, CT; AFS 25044, 25046)
    - Grandgent, C.H. (Folder 100)
      (Cambridge, MA; AFS 24875, 24877)
    - Grant, David A. (Folder 101)
      (Lyme, NH; AFS 25493, 25495)
    - Gregory, J. [John Gregory]. (Folder 102)
      (Winchendon, MA; AFS 24768, 24770)
    - Gregory, L. [Leslie Gregory]. (Folder 103)
      (Winchendon, MA; AFS 24772)
    - Gregory, R. [Ruth Gregory]; Lindstrom, D. [Dorothea Lindstrom]. (Folder 104)
      (Winchendon, MA; AFS 24774)
    - Guptill, L.M. [Lutie Martha Guptill]. (Folder 105)
      (Gouldsboro, ME; AFS 25213)
    - Guptill, M. [Marcus Guptill]. (Folder 106)
      (Gouldsboro, ME; AFS 25215, 25217)
    - Hagerman, F. [Frank Hagerman]. (Folder 107)
      (Hartland, New Brunswick, Canada; AFS 25278, 25280, 25282)
    - Hall, A.K. (Folder 108)
      (Windsor, VT; AFS 25498)
    - Hanners, A. (Folder 109)
      (Beverly, MA; AFS 24615)
    - Harlow, Mrs. A.J. and Harlow, Hiram. (Folder 110)
      (Shrewsbury, MA; AFS 24808-AFS 24811)
    - Hart, B. [Benjamin Hart]. (Folder 111)
      (Sutton, NH; AFS 25154, 25156, 25158)
    - Hayward, Mr. [Edward Hayward]. (Folder 112)
      (Keene, NH; AFS 25479)
    - Hayward, M.E. [Mary Ellen Hayward]. (Folder 113)
      (Keene, NH; AFS 25473, 25475, 25477)
    - Heath, Mrs. E.A. [Emily A. Heath]. (Box 20, Folder 114)
      (Wilmot Flat, NH; AFS 25145, 25148, 25150, 25152)
    - Hersey, F.A. [Frederick A. Hersey]. (Folder 115)
      (Hingham, MA; AFS 24742)
    - Hill, Mr. (Folder 116)
      (West Gouldsboro, ME; AFS 25220, 25222)
    - Hill, A. [Allen Hill]. (Folder 117)
      (St. Stephen, New Brunswick, Canada; AFS 25262)
    - Hill, Mrs. (Folder 118)
      (St. Stephen, New Brunswick, Canada; AFS 25258, 25260)
    - Hinckley, B. [Benjamin Hinckley]. (Folder 119)
      (Northampton, MA; AFS 24903, 24905)
    - Hinckley, B. Jr. [Ben Hinckley Jr.]. (Folder 120)
      (Northampton, MA; AFS 24907, 24909)
    - Hinckley, W. [Will Hinckley]. (Folder 121)
      (Blue Hill, ME; AFS 25203)
    - Hobbs, N.A. [Nellie A. Hobbs]. (Folder 122)
      (Candia Depot, NH; AFS 25129, 25132)
    - Hodgdon, Capt. (Folder 123)
      (Seal Cove, ME; AFS 25210)
    - Holland, W.A. (Folder 124)
      (Boston, MA; AFS 24524)
    - Horton, H.J. [Henry J. Horton]. (Folder 125)
      (Rehobeth, MA; AFS 24716, 24718)
    - House, E. [Elmore House]. (Folder 126)
      (Lincoln, ME; AFS 25296, 25298)
    - Howard, Mrs. R. [Howard, Mrs. Ray]. (Folder 127)
      (Foster, RI; AFS 24791, 24793)
    - Hubbard, J.T. [John T. Hubbard]. (Folder 128)
      (Litchfield, CT; AFS 25015, 25018, 25021, 25023)
    - Hubbard, R.E. [Richard E. Hubbard]. (Folder 129)
      (Shelburne, NH; AFS 25377, 25379, 25381)
    - Humphrey, C.W. [Chester W. Humphrey]. (Folder 130)
      (Rochester, MA; AFS 24699, 24701, 24703)
    - Jones, D. [Daniel Jones]. (Folder 131)
      (North Bradford (Clintonville), CT; AFS 24879, 24881, 24883
    - Ketchum, L. [Louise Ketchum]. (Folder 132)
      (St. John, New Brunswick, Canada; AFS 25264, 25266)
    - Kimball, W. [William Kimball]. (Folder 133)
      (Belmont, NH; AFS 25135, 25137, 25139, 25141)
    - Lamb, Mrs. A. [Adella Lamb]. (Folder 134)
      (Litchfield, CT; AFS 25052)
    - Lane, F.P. [Francis P. "Frank" Lane]. (Folder 135)
      (Red Beach, ME; AFS 25251, 25252)
    - Lapham, D. [Dana Lapham]. (Folder 136)
      (West Barnstable, MA; AFS 24680)
    - Lapham, H. [Harding Lapham]. (Folder 137)
      (West Barnstable, MA; AFS 24682)
    - Lathrop, E. [Elisha Lathrop]. (Folder 138)
      (Franklin, CT; AFS 25096, AFS 25098)
    - Laughlin, R.L. [Robina L. Laughlin]. (Folder 139)
      (Barnet, VT; AFS 25414, 25416, 25419, 25420)
    - Lindstrom, D. (Folder 140)
      See Gregory, R.
    - McIlvin, M. [Madison Preston McIlvin]. (Box 21, Folder 141)
      (McIlvin; Antrim, NH; AFS 25160, 25162)
    - McIntyre, E. (Folder 142)
      (Otnabog, New Brunswick, Canada; AFS 25270)
    - McLean, J.O. (Folder 143)
      (Glastonbury, CT; AFS 24841, 24843)
    - Mack, W.P. [Wallace Preston Mack]. (Folder 144)
      (Londonderry, NH; AFS 25406, 25407, 25408, 25409, 25410, 25411, 25412
    - Maddocks, Mrs. and Miss [Mrs. and Ella Maddocks] (Folder 145)
      (Owl's Head, ME; AFS 25199, 25201)
    - Meserve, Wm. H. [William H. Meserve]. (Folder 146)
      (Steep Falls, ME; AFS 25327)
    - Monson, E.H. [H. Edgar Monson]. (Folder 147)
      (Southbury, CT; AFS 25036, 25038)
    - Moorehead, M. (Folder 148)
      See Lamb, A.
    - Neptune, J. [Joseph Neptune]. (Folder 149)
      (Pleasant Point, ME; AFS 25245, 25247)
    - Noyes, J. (Folder 150)
      (Stonington, CT; AFS 24859, 24861, 24863)
    - Paige, A. [Alva Paige]. (Folder 151)
      (New Salem, MA; AFS 25504)
    - Paige, Bert. (Folder 152)
      (Antrim, NH; AFS 25164, 25166)
    - Paine, Mrs. S. [Sarah Paine]. (Folder 153)
      (Pomfret, CT; AFS 24820, 24821, 24824)
    - Page, Chas. P. [Charles P. Page]. (Folder 154)
      (Haverhill, NH; AFS 25459, 25461, 25463)
    - Palmer, B. [Ben Palmer]. (Folder 155)
      (Old Greenwich, CT; AFS 24705, 24711)
    - Partridge, H.W. [Harvey W. Partridge]. (Folder 156)
      (Pittsfield, MA; AFS 24929-24932)
    - Pearson, F.D. [Fred D. Pearson]. (Folder 157)
      (Newbury, MA; AFS 24590 - 24592)
    - Peck, H.S. and family [Howard S. Peck, Mrs. Peck, grandson]. (Folder 158)
      (Middletown, CT; AFS 25087 - 25089, 25091 - 25092, 25094
    - Perkins, K. [Katherine Perkins]. (Folder 159)
      (Conway, NH; AFS 25333)
    - Perry, M. [Marion Perry]. (Folder 160)
      (Hardwick, MA; AFS 24885, 24887)
    - Philbrook, (family of) [Elizabeth, Grenville, Helen, and Lawrence Philbrook]. (Folder 161)
      (Shelburne, NH; AFS 25385, 25387, 25389, 25391)
    - Philbrook, A.E. [Augustus E. Philbrook]. (Folder 162)
      (Shelburne, NH; AFS 25393, 25395, 25397)
    - Piage, Burt. (Folder 163)
      See Paige, Bert
    - Pinkham, T.S. (Folder 164)
      (Fort Kent, ME; AFS 25292)
    - Pratt, F. [Frank Pratt]. (Folder 165)
      (Old Saybrook, CT; AFS 24989, 24992, 24995)
    - Raddin, J.B. [Joseph B. Raddin]. (Box 22, Folder 166)
      (Groton, MA; AFS 24760, 24762, 24763)
    - Reinartz, J.L. [John L. Reinartz]. (Folder 167)
      (Manchester, CT; AFS 24850)
    - Richardson, Mrs. A.A. [Mrs. Arthur A. Richardson]. (Folder 168)
      (Stockbridge, MA; AFS 24937)
    - Robinson, G.A. [George A. Robinson]. (Folder 169)
      (Bennington, VT; AFS 25510)
    - Russell, T.M. (Folder 170)
      (Middletown, CT; AFS 25055, 25057, 25059, 25061 - 25064)
    - Sanborn, J.H. [John Henry Sanborn]. (Folder 171)
      (Acton Corner, ME; AFS 25305, 25307, 25309, 25311)
    - Schofield, E.L. [Ethel L. Schofield]. (Folder 172)
      (New Haven, CT; AFS 25085)
    - Sennett, Mr. (Folder 173)
      (Bailey's Island, ME; AFS 25191, AFS 25193)
    - Stevens, A. (Folder 174)
      See Giles, R.
    - Stevens, E. [H. Emagene Stevens]. (Folder 175)
      (Cummington, MA; AFS 24945, 24947, 24951)
    - Stevens, N.D. [Nellie D. Stevens]. (Folder 176)
      (Rockport, MA; AFS 24596, 24599, 24602)
    - Stevens, L.A. [Leon A. Stevens]. (Folder 177)
      (Cummington, MA; AFS 24939, 24941)
    - Stilwell, M. [Margaret Stilwell]. (Folder 178)
      (Providence, RI; AFS 24621, 24624)
    - Stone, C.A. [Charles A. Stone]. (Folder 179)
      (Andover, MA; AFS 24714)
    - Stone, C. Jr. [Charles Stone Jr.]. (Folder 180)
      (Andover, MA; AFS 24575)
    - Stone, E. [Elizabeth Stone]. (Folder 181)
      (Andover, MA; AFS 24573)
    - Stone, R.L. [Robert L. Stone]. (Folder 182)
      (Andover, MA; AFS 24521)
    - Stowell, R. [Ralph Stowell]. (Folder 183)
      (New Salem, MA; AFS 24922, 24925)
    - Trefethen, F.E. [Fred Ervine Trefethen]. (Folder 184)
      (Rye, NH; AFS 25116, 25118)
    - Troop, S. [Sam Troop]. (Folder 185)
      (Pittston, ME; AFS 25179, 25181)
    - Tucker, H.G. (Folder 186)
      (Foster, RI; AFS 24776, 24779)
    - Tucker, H.G. (Folder 187)
      (Foster, RI; AFS 24782, 24785, 24916)
    - Tucker, W. [Wilson Tucker]. (Folder 188)
      (Foster, RI; AFS 24788)
    - Tupper, Wm. [William Tupper]. (Folder 189)
      (Burlington, VT; AFS 25551, 25553)
    - Tutt, H. [Hannah Tutt]. (Folder 190)
      (Marblehead, MA; AFS 24866, 24869, 24872)
    - Warner, H.E. [Herbert E. Warner]. (Box 23, Folder 191)
      (Granby, MA; AFS 24895, 24898, 24900
    - Warren, Mr. and Mrs. [Harry and Mrs. Harry Warren]. (Folder 192)
      (Weston, MA; AFS 24543, 24545, 24547, 24548)
    - Washburn, R.E. [Ruth Ella Washburn]. (Folder 193)
      (Plymouth, MA; AFS 24696)
    - Weathern, B.F. [B.F. and Edna Jennie Weathern]. (Folder 194)
      (Farmington, ME; AFS 25369, 25371, 25371, 25375)
    - Weeden, Mrs. A.P. [Mrs. Arthur P. Weeden]. (Folder 195)
      (Providence, RI; AFS 24626, 24628, 24630)
    - Whitehall, M.G. [Martin G. Whitehall]. (Folder 196)
      (Ryegate, VT; AFS 25452, 25454, 25456)
    - Williams, M.S. [Mary Snow Williams]. (Folder 197)
      (Blue Hill, ME; AFS 25205, 25208)
    - York, A. [Abbie York]. (Folder 198)
      (Rockport, MA; AFS 24605, 24607, 24609)
    - Young, G.W. [George William Young]. (Folder 199)
      (Barrington, NH; AFS 25123, 25125)
  - Subject Cards (Box 24-25)
    Headings are in original order, rather than alphabetical order. Abbreviations for words and names have been spelled out in full.
    - Subject Cards (Box 24)
      Box 24: Headings: Topography, Weather, Farming, Implements, Vehicles, Butchering, Calls, Animals, Hunt-Fish, Trees-Flowers, Crops, Food, Cooking Utensils, Beverages, Dwellings, Buildings, Games, Amusements, Customs (Social), Olden Days, Fashions, Speech, Personalities, Lives, Illness and Medicine, Religion, Cemeteries, Education, Industries, Home Industries, Business Occupations
    - Subject Cards (Box 25)
      Box 25: Headings: Occupations, Roads-Travel, Economics-Politics, Family History, Local History, Civil War, Population
  - Index Cards (Box 26)
    2.5 linear inches of 3-inch x 5-inch index cards listing ADS Collection original numbers, informants' names, and quality of recordings.
    8.25 linear inches of 5-inch x 8-inch index cards listing AFS numbers, ADS Collection original numbers, informants' names, occupations, ages, recording locations, subjects, and notes about recordings. The information has been included in the ADS Collection database.
  - Tape Contents, Publications, and Reports
    - Tape Content Copies. (Box 27, Folder 200)
      Photocopies of labels of AFS preservation reel-to-reel tapes.
    - Obituaries. (Folder 201)
      Obituaries for Miles L. Hanley (1954) and Raven McDavid (1984-1985).
    - Bibliography, 1939-1984. (Folder 202)
      Citations for related publications.
    - Articles, Publications. (Folder 203)
      Publications about the ADS Collection.
    - Report on Hanley Collection. (Folder 204)
      A scholarly paper by Burr Angle and Richard Venesky of the University of Wisconsin. Includes two copies.
    - Library of Congress Publications. (Folder 205)
      Three copies of the Folklife Center News, Vol. 8, No. 2 (1985), and 3 copies of the Library of Congress Information Bulletin, Vol. 44, No. 1 (1985),. Both issues contain articles about the ADS Collection.
    - "The Hanley Tapes" (1974) (Folder 206)
      Two copies of a scholarly paper by Margaret Waterman (associate editor of DARE), of the University of Wisconsin.
    - "The Hanley Tapes" (1974), annotated. (Folder 207)
      One copy of a scholarly paper by Margaret Waterman (associate editor of DARE), of the University of Wisconsin. Annotated by "COL of KAL."
  - Presentation Events
    - Presentation Session Tapes. (Box 28, Folder 208)
      Manuscripts related to the presentation of the ADS Collection to the Library of Congress, December 28, 1984; see RWA 8547 for recording of Joe Hickerson's lecture.
    - Demonstration Collection Information, 1984-1985. (Folder 209)
      Manuscripts related to the demonstration of selected discs from the collection at the Library of Congress presentation event.
    - Correspondence: Presentation Event. (Folder 210)
      Correspondence related to the Library of Congress presentation event
    - Lists by Hanley of Discs and Transcripts. (Folder 211)
      Inventories of ADS Collection discs and related transcriptions held by Miles L. Hanley.
    - Presentation and Demo Tape Information. (Folder 212)
      Manuscripts related to the demonstration of selected discs from the collection, at the Library of Congress presentation.
    - Presentation Planning. (Folder 213)
      Manuscripts related to planning the presentation of the ADS Collection to the Library of Congress, December 28, 1984.
    - Presentation Events. (Folder 214)
      Manuscripts related to the presentation of the collection to the Library of Congress, December 28, 1984.
    - Speeches. (Folder 215)
      Copies of two speeches given at the presentation event, and notes related to the collection and event, written by Joseph C. Hickerson
    - Presentation Publicity. (Folder 216)
      Publications, press releases, and other manuscripts related to the presentation event.
    - ADS Centennial Information on Commemorative Cassettes. (Folder 217)
      Manuscripts related to audiocassette commemorating the centennial of the American Dialect Society, 1889-1989, plus one copy of the audiocassette.
    - Handouts/ARSC Meeting, 1990. (Folder 218)
      Manuscripts related to a discussion of the collection by the Association for Recorded Sound Collections, February 26, 1990.
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  The American Dialect Society Collection's recordings consist of 891 aluminum, aluminum-based acetate, plastic, and shellac disc recordings. Also included are one 10-inch preservation reel containing 18 recordings, and one audiocassette of presentation event recordings. In addition, there are 78 10-inch preservation reels.
  869 audio discs (most originals, and some copies that stand in for original recordings no longer with the collection) were digitized in 2003 and 2004. See Series IV (Electronic Media) for more details.
  There are also 22 discs that were not digitized, because they are duplicates of recordings in the collection that were digitized. The copies have been kept with the collection. Correspondence related to these discs is found in the case file. The discs are in the physical custody of M/B/RS.
  The American Dialect Society centennial commemorative cassette is located in Box 28.
- Series III: Graphic Images
  - Photographic Items, n.d. (Folder 13)
    PH01. Miles Hanley (black-and-white). 1 photograph
    PH02. Raven McDavid (black-and-white). 1 photograph
    PH03. Professor Hanley's Photographic Equipment; this photocopy of a photograph shows disc-cutting equipment, a microphone stand, and a briefcase. 1 photocopy.
- Series IV: Electronic Media (Box 1)
  Only the audio discs from this collection have been digitized. For each digital transfer, the following formats have been created:
  1) An uncompressed master recording (a WAV file, at 96/24)
  2) A compressed derivative (a WAV file, at 44.1/16)
  3) A compressed derivative (an mp3, at 256 kbps)
  1 Zip disc labeled "American Dialect Society Collection Documents"; this includes the collection guide, worksheets from Cutting Corp. with information regarding digitization work, etc.
Appendix A: Audio Disc Recordings By Format
Note: The digital ID for each item is constructed from the collection number and the AFS number; e.g., AFS 25036 becomes afc1984011/25036, AFS 24469 becomes afc1984011/24469, etc.
Audio discs (digitized)
679 12-inch aluminum (originals) M/B/RS See ADS Collection database for details.
46 12-inch aluminum (duplicates) M/B/RS AFS 25036, 25038, 25091, 25618, 25619, 25620, 25642-25675, 25747, 25763-25767
1 12-inch aluminum (original and duplicate) M/B/RS AFS 25046 (Side A is a copy, Side B is original)
7 12-inch aluminum (version unknown) M/B/RS AFS 25551, 25553; others
18 10-inch aluminum (originals) M/B/RS AFS 24469, 24470, 24472-24478, 24486, 24489, 24490, 24492, 24495, 24500, 24501, 24503, 24504
1 10-inch aluminum (version unknown) M/B/RS AFS 25624
34 8-inch aluminum (originals) M/B/RS AFS 24513, 24515, 24536, 24542, 24583, 24595, 24617, 24650, 24680, 24682, 24698, 24774, 24790, 24921, 24967, 24987, 25006, 25035, 25052, 25085, 25122, 25290, 25291, 25311, 25327, 25337, 25351, 25381, 25402, 25470-25472, 25607, 26003
1 8-inch aluminum (copy) M/B/RS AFS 24917
1 7-inch aluminum (original) M/B/RS AFS 24494
3 6-inch aluminum (originals) M/B/RS AFS 25994, 25995, 25996
44 12-inch acetate (originals) M/B/RS AFS 25679-25722
9 12-inch acetate (duplicates) M/B/RS AFS 25730, 25732, 25736, 25737, 25744, 25751, 25754, 25757, 25761
2 10-inch acetate (originals) M/B/RS AFS 25723, 25993
1 6-inch acetate (original) M/B/RS AFS 26002
1 12-inch plastic (duplicate) M/B/RS AFS 25998
1 11-inch plastic (duplicate) M/B/RS AFS 25997
13 10-inch shellac (duplicates) M/B/RS AFS 26004-26016
6 unknown size/format (version unknown) M/B/RS See ADS Collection database for details.
Audio discs ( not digitized)
19 12-inch aluminum (duplicates) M/B/RS AFS 24471, 24645, 24710, 24728, 24798, 24865, 24915, 25003, 25030, 25045, 25090, 25109, 25136, 25163, 25218, 25299, 25326, 25552, 25554
1 10-inch aluminum (duplicate) M/B/RS AFS 25625
1 10-inch shellac (duplicate) M/B/RS AFS 26008
1 8-inch aluminum (duplicate) M/B/RS AFS 24917
Appendix B: Locations
Australia
Canada
New Brunswick
Brighton
Carleton County
Charlotte County
Hartland
Queens County
Saint Croix River Region
St. Andrews
Saint John
St. John County
St. Stephen
Victoria County
Woodstock
Newfoundland and Labrador
Labrador City
Nova Scotia
Quebec
Montreal
Quebec City
China
Denmark
England
Cornwall
Lancashire
Liverpool
London
Plymouth
Southern England
Yorkshire
France
Germany
Greenland
Ireland
Castleisland
Mexico
New Zealand
Norway
Scotland
South Africa
Cape of Good Hope
KwaZulu-Natal (Province)
Sweden
United States
Alabama
Connecticut
Abington
Bantam
Bethel
Canterbury
Clintonville
Cornwall
Danbury
Derby
East Hartford
East Hartland
East Village SEE Winsted
Essex
Fairfield
Farmington
Franklin
Glastonbury
Granby
Greenwich
Hart Bridge SEE West Cornwall
Hartford
Hart's Bridge SEE West Cornwall
Laurel City SEE Winsted
Litchfield
Lyme
Manchester
Middletown
Milford
Morris
New Fairfield
New Haven
New London
North Branford
Old Greenwich
Old Saybrook
Packerville
Pomfret
Prospect Mountain
Redding Ridge
Sharon
Southbury
Stonington
Tolland
Wallingford
Warren [Litchfield County]
West Cornwall [also called Hart Bridge or Hart's Bridge ]
West Hartford
Weston
Winsted [also called East Village or Laurel City ]
Wolcott
Georgia
Brewers Neck SEE Broro Neck
Broro Neck [also called Brewers Neck ]
Harris Neck
Saint Simons Island
Sapelo Island
Illinois
Bismarck
Kansas
Kentucky
Louisiana
Baton Rouge
Maine
Acton
Ashland
Bailey Island
Beal Island
Biddeford
Biddeford Pool [also known as Fletcher Neck or Winter Harbor ]
Blue Hill
Bog Brook [Washington County]
Brewer
Brooklin
Burnham
Calais [also known as Kallus ]
Cambridge
Cape Neddick [also known as Cape Nuddike, Neddock Cape, or Nedick Cape ]
Cape Nuddike SEE Cape Neddick
Cumberland
Ellsworth
Farmington
Fletcher Neck SEE Biddeford Pool
Fort Fairfield
Fort Kent
Frankfort
Gouldsboro [also known as West Bay ]
Harpswell
Houlton
Jonesboro
Jonesport
Kallus SEE Calais
Limington
Lincoln
Loon Lake
Lubec
Machias
Machiasport
Milburn SEE Skowhegan
Mount Katahdin
Nanrantsouak SEE Norridgewock
Nanrantsouk SEE Norridgewock
Nedick Cape SEE Cape Neddick
Neddock Cape SEE Cape Neddick
Neriwocke SEE Norridgewock
New Sweden
Newport
Norridgewock [also known as Nanrantsouk, Nanrantsouak, or Neriwocke ]
North Lubec
Northeast Harbor
Orono
Owls Head
Penobscot
Pittston
Pleasant Point
Portland
Red Beach
Rockland
Rogues Bluff SEE Roque Bluffs
Roque Bluffs [also known as Rogues Bluff ]
Seal Cove
Searsport
Skowhegan [also known as Milburn ]
Sprucehead Island
Standish
Steep Falls
West Bay SEE Gouldsboro
West Farmington
West Gouldsboro
Yarmouth [also known as Yarmouthville, Yarmouth Village, or Yarmoutville ]
Yarmouthville SEE Yarmouth
Yarmouth Village SEE Yarmouth
Yarmoutville SEE Yarmouth
Maryland
Baltimore
Massachusetts
Andover
Barnstable
Beverly
Billerica
Boston
Brookline
Byfield
Cambridge
Cape Cod
Chelsea
Cheshire
Cohasset
Colrain
Concord
Cummington
Danvers
Eastham [also known as Nauset or Nawsett ]
Edgartown
Granby
Groton
Hardwick
Hingham
Makonikey [also known as Necankney Cliff or Norton Point ]
Marblehead
Marion
Martha's Vineyard
Mill River [Berkshire County]
Milton
Nantucket (Town)
Nantucket Island
Nauset SEE Eastham
Nawsett SEE Eastham
Necankney Cliff SEE Makonikey
New Bedford
New Marlborough
New Salem
Newbury
Newburyport
Newton
North Truro
Northampton
Norton Point SEE Makonikey
Palmer
Pittsfield
Plymouth
Raynham Center
Rehoboth
Rochester
Rockport
Salem
Saugus
Sconset SEE Siasconset
Sharon
Sherborn
Shrewsbury
Siasconset [also known as Sconset ]
South Westport
South Williamstown
Spencer
Springfield
Stockbridge
Taunton
Topsfield
Truro
West Barnstable
West Tisbury
Weston
Westport–Horse Neck [not found]
Williamstown
Winchendon
Worcester
Missouri
Kirksville
Lincoln County
Saint Louis
New England
New Hampshire
Amherst
Antrim
Barrington
Bedford
Belmont
Canaan
Candia Depot
Center Conway
Conway
East Barrington
Gorham
Haverhill
Keene
Kingston
Laconia
Lancaster
Londonderry
Lyme [also known as Lyme Plain ]
Lyme Plain SEE Lyme
Madbury
Marlow
Mount Washington
Nashua
North Branch [Hillsborough County]
Plymouth
Rye
Seabrook
Shelburne
Sutton
Wilmot
Wilmot Flat
New York (State)
Middletown
New York (City)
New York (City) East Side
Plattsburgh
North Carolina
Louisburg
Ohio
Rockbridge
Pennsylvania
Pottsville
Susquehanna
Rhode Island
Chepachet
East Greenwich
Foster
Foster Center
Narragansett
Newport
Point Judith
Providence
Richmond [Washington County]
South Foster
Wyoming
South Carolina
Charleston
Edisto Island
Frogmore
Greenville
Johns Island
Saint Helena Island
Wadmalaw Island
Wedgefield
Tennessee
Texas
Dallas
McDade
Paris
Waco
Vermont
Bennington
Brattleboro
Burlington
East Calais
Ferrisburg SEE Ferrisburgh
Ferrisburgh [Also known as Ferrisburg ]
North Ferrisburg SEE North Ferrisburgh
North Ferrisburgh [Also known as North Ferrisburgh ]
Northfield
Pawlet
Plymouth
Ryegate SEE Ryegate Corner
Ryegate Corner [Also known as Ryegate ]
Saint Johnsbury
Saint Johnsbury Center
Shaftsbury
Stockbridge
Wallingford
West Brattleboro
Windsor
Virginia
Albemarle County
Altavista [Campbell County]
Brays [Essex County]
Buena Vista [King and Queen County]
Charlottesville
Dunnsville [Essex County]
Fredericksburg
Harrison